At the beginning of every term we invite new students and their parents
ボドウェルでは、毎学期、新入生とその両親を
for a comprehensive new student orientation where they can tour the facilities
学校見学も含めた新入生オリエンテーションへ招きます
and attend various presentations to help prepare them for the year
オリエンテーションでは、学校生活で必要な、さまざまなプレゼンテーションを行っています。
New students and parents begin by checking in couple of days before the orientation starts.
新入生は、オリエンテーションが始まる2、3日前に寮へチェックインが可能です。
It's a busy time of the year. It's time to mingle meet other - especially the volunteers
オリエンテーションは毎回とても忙しいスケジュールですが、色々な人達と交流するいい機会でもあります - 特にボランティア生徒
and to also meet the boarding staff will help direct you over the next couple of days
また、寮スタッフと交流することで、学校が始まるまでの2、3日の間に色々な案内も可能になります
Depending on when you arrive you will have a couple of days to relax and unpack
到着日によっては、荷物の整理や時差ボケがとれるのには、数日かかります
Take a tour of the facility
学校内を見学してみてください。
Meet staff and student volunteers that will guide you on a tour of Bodwell or help direct you where to go
Bodwellの学生ボランティアも、色々お手伝いをしてくれます
There are lots of signs around the school to help you as well we have coffee we have snacks available
学校内には、さまざまな案内のサインがあります。
As orientation begins it's an extremely busy time for new students and their parents
オリエンテーションの日は、忙しいスケジュールになります
However, it is all done in a relaxed atmosphere and we accommodate and appreciate that everybody is new.
ただ、私たちも皆さんが緊張しているのは理解していますので、安心してください
So we're here to offer help the students to adjust
私たちは学生がスムーズに初日を過ごせる様、ここにいます
When orientation begins students and parents will have to follow different schedules during this time, it's a very busy schedule for students
オリエンテーション日は、色々な事をこなす必要があります
They have to meet the principals and admin
校長や副校長、教頭、寮スタッフなどに会います
they have to do a placement test
英語のテストもあります
They will attend the citizenship presentation where they'll be exposed to various leadership activities around school
そのほか、学校の規則についての説明、クラブ活動、ボランティア活動などの説明を受けます
They'll be fitted for their uniform
制服の試着・支給も行われます
They will attend a laptop distribution session and you'll be briefed about how to use their new laptops.
学校仕様のラップトップの支給、使用方法についての説明をうけます
They'll attend presentation on safety
安全に関するプレゼンテーションや
They will also attend a presentation about Block E
土曜日クラスについてのプレゼンテーションもあります
and extracurricular activities and various athletic teams around school. They will do a neighborhood walk
課外活動や様々なスポーツチームの説明や、学校周りの散策もあります
So they're familiar with the school and its surroundings
また、学校やカリキュラムに関して
They will attend a group orientation with their counselors followed by one-on-one for their course selection
カウンセラーから、グループオリエンテーションを受け、その後コース選択を一対一でおこないます
They will also attend boarding life and house orientations
滞在についてのオリエンテーションもあります
We also help our students with opening a bank account by inviting one of the local banks to come to Bodwell
また、希望があれば、銀行口座を開設することも可能です
Parents will have their own separate schedule. They to get to meet the principals and the admin team
保護者の方は、生徒とは別に、校長、副校長、教頭、寮スタッフに会う機会があります
They attend a presentation about boarding and homestay programs
寮やホームステイプログラムについてのプレゼンテーションもあります
They tour the City of North Vancouver Vancouver and West Vancouver
また、保護者の方へは、ノースバンクーバーとウエストバンクーバーの街の見学ツアーもあります
They attend orientation with counselors and they can request one-on-one meeting with their counselors
保護者とカウンセラーとのオリエンテーション、希望があれば、カウンセラーと一対一のミーティングもアレンジができます
they get a chance to network with other parents and with school administrators and
オリエンテーション中、他の保護者や学校スタッフと交流する機会が沢山あります
They also attend a presentation about graduation requirements and post-secondary discussion
卒業基準や大学進学に関してのプレゼンテーションもおこなわれます
There are many activities parents and students do together - a briefing by the police department
また、地元警察からの安全に関しての説明会には、生徒と一緒に参加していただきます
Start of the term assembly and most mealtimes are spent together
学校初日の全校集会やオリエンテーション中の食事は、生徒さんと一緒にとって頂けます
During orientation is a lot to take in but be assured
オリエンテーション中は、色々な事があり、分からない事も多いと思いますが、
there is lots of time to say goodbye to your child meet the staff who will take care of your child and
子供さんとお別れをする時間も十分ありますし、生徒さんのお世話をさせて頂く寮のスタッフなどとも会って頂く事ができます
Meet other parents and families who are also new to the Bodwell community
他の生徒さんのご家族などとも、沢山交流して頂き、
You
ボドウェルコミュニティーを楽しんで頂ければと願っています